{
    "subject": "resource/Reichskommissariat_Ostland",
    "predicate": "ontology/capital",
    "object": "resource/Riga",
    "human_readable": "The capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland is Riga.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9799860715866089,
            "question": "Is Riga still the capital of the former Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.975028932094574,
            "question": "During what historical period was Riga the capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9661760330200195,
            "question": "What is the capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9608076810836792,
            "question": "What is the current status of Riga's historical significance as the capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9588596820831299,
            "question": "What major events took place in Riga during its time as the capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9122079610824585,
            "question": "What can we learn about the history and politics of Europe from the fact that Riga was the capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7843475341796875,
            "question": "What was Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5950357913970947,
            "question": "How did the role of Riga change after the end of Reichskommissariat Ostland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5239905118942261,
            "question": "Where is Riga located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4109915494918823,
            "question": "What other cities served as capitals in that region before Riga?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland is Riga.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8962_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where is Riga located?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8962_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the role of Riga change after the end of Reichskommissariat Ostland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8962_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was Reichskommissariat Ostland?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8962_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8962_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the context information, I can conclude that:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe reason for this answer is that the document mentions \"only the (Latvian) capital city of Riga (Gebiet Riga Stadt) was directly administered by the Reichskommissar f\u00fcr das Ostland.\" and also mentions \"Generalbezirk Lettland (Latvia)[...] District seat: Riga\". These phrases clearly indicate that Riga is indeed the capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents mention that \"only the (Latvian) capital city of Riga (Gebiet Riga Stadt) was directly administered by the Reichskommissar f\u00fcr das Ostland,\" which supports the statement that the capital of Reichskommissariat Ostland is Riga."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}